[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 30, "question": "Dana, one question really, amongst other things he may have been eating, can we include magic mushrooms?", "question_tokens": ["Dana", ",", "one", "question", "really", ",", "amongst", "other", "things", "he", "may", "have", "been", "eating", ",", "can", "we", "include", "magic", "mushrooms", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NN", "RB", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBG", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 31, "answer": "I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dana"]}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "RB", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 40, "question": "Why put Congress through this?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "put", "Congress", "through", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 41, "answer": "But Dana actually, with respect I disagree with your premise.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "Dana", "actually", ",", "with", "respect", "I", "disagree", "with", "your", "premise", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ted Cruz"], "LOCATION": ["Texas"]}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "``", "NN", "''", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "I mean, look and even the senior members of your own party led by John McCain and others lambaste you as wasting everybody's time, doesn't it just park you into the delusion and ridiculous category?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "look", "and", "even", "the", "senior", "members", "of", "your", "own", "party", "led", "by", "John", "McCain", "and", "others", "lambaste", "you", "as", "wasting", "everybody", "'s", "time", ",", "does", "n't", "it", "just", "park", "you", "into", "the", "delusion", "and", "ridiculous", "category", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "CC", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "POS", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "Not if you're somebody like Ted Cruz who won his election last year in upset against in a \"establishment\" Republican in Texas and has made it his mission to rock the boat and not let go of this ObamaCare issue.", "answer_tokens": ["Not", "if", "you", "'re", "somebody", "like", "Ted", "Cruz", "who", "won", "his", "election", "last", "year", "in", "upset", "against", "in", "a", "``", "establishment", "''", "Republican", "in", "Texas", "and", "has", "made", "it", "his", "mission", "to", "rock", "the", "boat", "and", "not", "let", "go", "of", "this", "ObamaCare", "issue", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John McCain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 90, "question": "What's wrong with that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "wrong", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 91, "answer": "There's nothing wrong with that, but the problem is that ObamaCare try to fix the system for people that didn't need a fix, and it's too big, it's too costly.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "nothing", "wrong", "with", "that", ",", "but", "the", "problem", "is", "that", "ObamaCare", "try", "to", "fix", "the", "system", "for", "people", "that", "did", "n't", "need", "a", "fix", ",", "and", "it", "'s", "too", "big", ",", "it", "'s", "too", "costly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Do you think it's at all possible that he has the votes to win this battle?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "at", "all", "possible", "that", "he", "has", "the", "votes", "to", "win", "this", "battle", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Marc, I think that's funny the hypocrisy ...", "answer_tokens": ["Marc", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "funny", "the", "hypocrisy", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 163, "question": "Can you answer that question though?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "answer", "that", "question", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 164, "answer": "I'm going to answer it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "going", "to", "answer", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 165, "question": "Could you answer that question though?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "answer", "that", "question", "though", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 166, "answer": "I'm answering it right now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "answering", "it", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Are we heading to a new relationship?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "heading", "to", "a", "new", "relationship", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "The honest answer is right now we don't know but it's worth testing.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "honest", "answer", "is", "right", "now", "we", "do", "n't", "know", "but", "it", "'s", "worth", "testing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 258, "question": "But in light of all that's been going on, is the President's position now the correct one going forward?", "question_tokens": ["But", "in", "light", "of", "all", "that", "'s", "been", "going", "on", ",", "is", "the", "President", "'s", "position", "now", "the", "correct", "one", "going", "forward", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CD", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 259, "answer": "Yes, because again, I think it's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "because", "again", ",", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "And would you trust Vladimir Putin?", "question_tokens": ["And", "would", "you", "trust", "Vladimir", "Putin", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "We should be extremely cautious again on the process of verification.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "should", "be", "extremely", "cautious", "again", "on", "the", "process", "of", "verification", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Vladimir Putin"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 277, "question": "Had you been British Prime Minister, would you have pushed very hard to do military action at that time?", "question_tokens": ["Had", "you", "been", "British", "Prime", "Minister", ",", "would", "you", "have", "pushed", "very", "hard", "to", "do", "military", "action", "at", "that", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 278, "answer": "I would certainly push hard to be with America as an ally at this moment.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "certainly", "push", "hard", "to", "be", "with", "America", "as", "an", "ally", "at", "this", "moment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 346, "question": "Let's start with the two boys here, Khalid what were you were doing and describe what this gun is?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "start", "with", "the", "two", "boys", "here", ",", "Khalid", "what", "were", "you", "were", "doing", "and", "describe", "what", "this", "gun", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NNP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "CC", "VB", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 347, "answer": "It's an airsoft gun.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "an", "airsoft", "gun", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "Is it a toy?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "a", "toy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "Yes sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Do you think anything you were doing was wrong Aidan?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "anything", "you", "were", "doing", "was", "wrong", "Aidan", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBD", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "Well, yes but I don't think it has to do anything with school.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "yes", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "has", "to", "do", "anything", "with", "school", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Aidan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NN", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "TO", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "OK, what do you think you were doing that was wrong?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "you", "were", "doing", "that", "was", "wrong", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "Well, we were shooting airsoft guns when we we're not supposed to do because our parents did not want us to.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "were", "shooting", "airsoft", "guns", "when", "we", "we", "'re", "not", "supposed", "to", "do", "because", "our", "parents", "did", "not", "want", "us", "to", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "Tell me first of all did you know that he had this toy gun and what is your view of it?", "question_tokens": ["Tell", "me", "first", "of", "all", "did", "you", "know", "that", "he", "had", "this", "toy", "gun", "and", "what", "is", "your", "view", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "OLANGEL CARABALLO: Well, I purchased the gun but -- when I purchase the toy and I just purchased that and he wasn't supposed to be playing with it at that time.", "answer_tokens": ["OLANGEL", "CARABALLO", ":", "Well", ",", "I", "purchased", "the", "gun", "but", "--", "when", "I", "purchase", "the", "toy", "and", "I", "just", "purchased", "that", "and", "he", "was", "n't", "supposed", "to", "be", "playing", "with", "it", "at", "that", "time", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 362, "question": "Do you have any problem intrinsically with him using that particular toy gun?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "problem", "intrinsically", "with", "him", "using", "that", "particular", "toy", "gun", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 363, "answer": "Oh no.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "JJ", "TO", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "OK, well let's bring in Tim Clark, your son oversee (ph) Aidan has also been heavily punished here, what is your view about what the school has done?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "well", "let", "'s", "bring", "in", "Tim", "Clark", ",", "your", "son", "oversee", "(", "ph", ")", "Aidan", "has", "also", "been", "heavily", "punished", "here", ",", "what", "is", "your", "view", "about", "what", "the", "school", "has", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "VB", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", ":", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "VBN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "I'm just amazed that they feel that they're more suitable to discipline my child than I am.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "just", "amazed", "that", "they", "feel", "that", "they", "'re", "more", "suitable", "to", "discipline", "my", "child", "than", "I", "am", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tim Clark", "Aidan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 373, "question": "Now, if any of these kids as far as you're aware Mr. Clark did any of them complain to the school about what happened?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "if", "any", "of", "these", "kids", "as", "far", "as", "you", "'re", "aware", "Mr.", "Clark", "did", "any", "of", "them", "complain", "to", "the", "school", "about", "what", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 374, "answer": "No, they did not.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "they", "did", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Clark"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Now, were you aware of all those incidents Mrs. Caraballo and what is your reaction to the school making that public?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "were", "you", "aware", "of", "all", "those", "incidents", "Mrs.", "Caraballo", "and", "what", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "the", "school", "making", "that", "public", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "Oh, I'm -- I never signed a waiver for them to go public.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "'m", "--", "I", "never", "signed", "a", "waiver", "for", "them", "to", "go", "public", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mrs. Caraballo"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "Have you've been a naughty boy?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "'ve", "been", "a", "naughty", "boy", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "I mean I don't know how you feel about being a naughty boy, but I don't -- I do know that I have been in trouble in recent times.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "how", "you", "feel", "about", "being", "a", "naughty", "boy", ",", "but", "I", "do", "n't", "--", "I", "do", "know", "that", "I", "have", "been", "in", "trouble", "in", "recent", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 386, "question": "And why is that do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "why", "is", "that", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 387, "answer": "Because I have a little bit of a temper.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "have", "a", "little", "bit", "of", "a", "temper", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "And are you working to trying to deal with that?", "question_tokens": ["And", "are", "you", "working", "to", "trying", "to", "deal", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Yes sir.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "sir", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 390, "question": "OK, Aidan are you working to deal with your -- I don't know what your problem is, you don't seem to have the same disciplinary record, have you've been naughty as well or not?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "Aidan", "are", "you", "working", "to", "deal", "with", "your", "--", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "what", "your", "problem", "is", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "seem", "to", "have", "the", "same", "disciplinary", "record", ",", "have", "you", "'ve", "been", "naughty", "as", "well", "or", "not", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WP", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 391, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Aidan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "So, you probably is that you really gone too far, right?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "probably", "is", "that", "you", "really", "gone", "too", "far", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 394, "question": "So, you're both going to be better boys and hope to get back to school as soon as possible?", "question_tokens": ["So", ",", "you", "'re", "both", "going", "to", "be", "better", "boys", "and", "hope", "to", "get", "back", "to", "school", "as", "soon", "as", "possible", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RB", "TO", "NN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 395, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [",", "DT", "CD", "NNP", ":", "NNPS", ",", "PRP", ":", "RB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "OK, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["OK", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": ", THE 5 BROWNS: Yes, we -- actually when we have musical disagreements, we usually will take a vote and luckily there's an odd number of us because usually majority wins.", "answer_tokens": [",", "THE", "5", "BROWNS", ":", "Yes", ",", "we", "--", "actually", "when", "we", "have", "musical", "disagreements", ",", "we", "usually", "will", "take", "a", "vote", "and", "luckily", "there", "'s", "an", "odd", "number", "of", "us", "because", "usually", "majority", "wins", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["OK"]}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [",", "DT", "CD", "NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 427, "question": "If you all went head to head on America's got Talent, who would win?", "question_tokens": ["If", "you", "all", "went", "head", "to", "head", "on", "America", "'s", "got", "Talent", ",", "who", "would", "win", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 428, "answer": ", THE 5 BROWNS: Yeah, OK, so it's funny because people come unto us after concerts and every night it's always different.", "answer_tokens": [",", "THE", "5", "BROWNS", ":", "Yeah", ",", "OK", ",", "so", "it", "'s", "funny", "because", "people", "come", "unto", "us", "after", "concerts", "and", "every", "night", "it", "'s", "always", "different", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": [",", "DT", "CD", "NNP", ":", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "Are the girls better than the boys?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "the", "girls", "better", "than", "the", "boys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NNS", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": ", THE 5 BROWNS: No, I don't think.", "answer_tokens": [",", "THE", "5", "BROWNS", ":", "No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 446, "question": "And who's the most competitive?", "question_tokens": ["And", "who", "'s", "the", "most", "competitive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 447, "answer": "Gregory is pretty competitive, yeah.", "answer_tokens": ["Gregory", "is", "pretty", "competitive", ",", "yeah", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 452, "question": "An awful thing about the worst thing that you could possibly imagine, the moment that you all realized what have been going on, how did you deal with it as siblings?", "question_tokens": ["An", "awful", "thing", "about", "the", "worst", "thing", "that", "you", "could", "possibly", "imagine", ",", "the", "moment", "that", "you", "all", "realized", "what", "have", "been", "going", "on", ",", "how", "did", "you", "deal", "with", "it", "as", "siblings", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBD", "WP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 453, "answer": "Well, you know, the moment I realized that my sisters have been abused and it wasn't just me, it was probably the worst moment of my life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "the", "moment", "I", "realized", "that", "my", "sisters", "have", "been", "abused", "and", "it", "was", "n't", "just", "me", ",", "it", "was", "probably", "the", "worst", "moment", "of", "my", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "CC", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 459, "question": "How do you feel about it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 460, "answer": "You know time is so important and, you know, that I've had a couple of years now to sort of deal with it all and process it.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "time", "is", "so", "important", "and", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "I", "'ve", "had", "a", "couple", "of", "years", "now", "to", "sort", "of", "deal", "with", "it", "all", "and", "process", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 463, "question": "Deondra, what are your feelings towards your father?", "question_tokens": ["Deondra", ",", "what", "are", "your", "feelings", "towards", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "NNS", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 464, "answer": "Well, I mean, obviously, you know, that they are your parents.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "obviously", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "they", "are", "your", "parents", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 468, "question": "You have -- do any of you have any contact with him at all?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "--", "do", "any", "of", "you", "have", "any", "contact", "with", "him", "at", "all", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "VBP", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 469, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "And let me bring one of the boys in, Ryan (inaudible) talk to you to -- how do you feel about your mother, how did she feel about what happened to your father?", "question_tokens": ["And", "let", "me", "bring", "one", "of", "the", "boys", "in", ",", "Ryan", "(", "inaudible", ")", "talk", "to", "you", "to", "--", "how", "do", "you", "feel", "about", "your", "mother", ",", "how", "did", "she", "feel", "about", "what", "happened", "to", "your", "father", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", "TO", ":", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "I have minimal contact with my mom just to check up on her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "minimal", "contact", "with", "my", "mom", "just", "to", "check", "up", "on", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Is that the same to all of you?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "same", "to", "all", "of", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "It's just sort of disappointing that she hasn't really felt -- it's been -- she hasn't been terribly supportive of us and that's disappointing to us.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "just", "sort", "of", "disappointing", "that", "she", "has", "n't", "really", "felt", "--", "it", "'s", "been", "--", "she", "has", "n't", "been", "terribly", "supportive", "of", "us", "and", "that", "'s", "disappointing", "to", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 483, "question": "But, do you feel you can have a reconcile with your mother or your father properly?", "question_tokens": ["But", ",", "do", "you", "feel", "you", "can", "have", "a", "reconcile", "with", "your", "mother", "or", "your", "father", "properly", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 484, "answer": "It's hard to say, you know, I mean, they're -- I think when it comes to like forgiveness and relationships, it's a personal thing for each of us.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "hard", "to", "say", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "they", "'re", "--", "I", "think", "when", "it", "comes", "to", "like", "forgiveness", "and", "relationships", ",", "it", "'s", "a", "personal", "thing", "for", "each", "of", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "Have they ever apologized to you?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "they", "ever", "apologized", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I think you feel when somebody is truly penitent.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "feel", "when", "somebody", "is", "truly", "penitent", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "How about that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "Sounds good.", "answer_tokens": ["Sounds", "good", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Carnegie Hall"]}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Let's talk about Carnegie Hall, Deondra?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "talk", "about", "Carnegie", "Hall", ",", "Deondra", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "It's amazing after everything that we've been through especially over the last couple of years to be able to live our dream and perform in Carnegie Hall, we have a new album that's coming out that was a dream project that we've wanted to do our whole performing lives.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "amazing", "after", "everything", "that", "we", "'ve", "been", "through", "especially", "over", "the", "last", "couple", "of", "years", "to", "be", "able", "to", "live", "our", "dream", "and", "perform", "in", "Carnegie", "Hall", ",", "we", "have", "a", "new", "album", "that", "'s", "coming", "out", "that", "was", "a", "dream", "project", "that", "we", "'ve", "wanted", "to", "do", "our", "whole", "performing", "lives", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Carnegie Hall"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "Yeah and Ryan, I mean how much has it been a healing thing for you as a group of five siblings, what do you say?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", "and", "Ryan", ",", "I", "mean", "how", "much", "has", "it", "been", "a", "healing", "thing", "for", "you", "as", "a", "group", "of", "five", "siblings", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "That music is a healing for all of us I think and individually and as a group.", "answer_tokens": ["That", "music", "is", "a", "healing", "for", "all", "of", "us", "I", "think", "and", "individually", "and", "as", "a", "group", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Ryan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "Has that been equally helpful to you guys?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "that", "been", "equally", "helpful", "to", "you", "guys", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "Oh, it's been hugely -- our faith has been so important us.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "it", "'s", "been", "hugely", "--", "our", "faith", "has", "been", "so", "important", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Foundation for Survivors of Abuse"]}, "docId": "130924pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "RP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "CC", "PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "And tell me quickly about the foundation that you two set this up, right?", "question_tokens": ["And", "tell", "me", "quickly", "about", "the", "foundation", "that", "you", "two", "set", "this", "up", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "CD", "JJ", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "The Foundation for Survivors of Abuse was set up Desirae and I and we -- it's important to us that people have the timeline to be able to heal when they're ready and with the laws and statutes of limitations on how they are, sometimes that is not the case.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "Foundation", "for", "Survivors", "of", "Abuse", "was", "set", "up", "Desirae", "and", "I", "and", "we", "--", "it", "'s", "important", "to", "us", "that", "people", "have", "the", "timeline", "to", "be", "able", "to", "heal", "when", "they", "'re", "ready", "and", "with", "the", "laws", "and", "statutes", "of", "limitations", "on", "how", "they", "are", ",", "sometimes", "that", "is", "not", "the", "case", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]